Stanford University, Office of Student Activities, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional material, 1978-2004; Accession ARCH.2014-052
  - Volunteer student organization files, 1978-2004
    - Active, Stanford, 1978-2004
      - Stanford Alpine Ski Team, 1983-2002 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Stanford Solar Car Project, 1991-2003 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Stanford Special Olympics, 1982-2001 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Stanford Speedskating, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Stanford Spoken Word Collective, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Stanford Student Golf Club SSGC, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Stanford Square Dancers, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Stanford Steppers, 1998-2002 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Stanford Students for Life, 1986-2002 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Stanford Student Nat'l Medical Association, 1988-2003 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Stanford Swing Kids Club, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Stanford Tae Kwon Do Club, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Stanford Taiko Group, 1991-2002 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Stanford Tech Law Review, 1998-2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Stanford Taiwanese Student Association, 1978-2002 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Stanford Tango Club, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Stanford Tennis Club, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Stanford Texas Club, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Stanford Triathalon Club, 1992-2003 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Stanford Turkish Student Association, 1990-2002 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Stanford Undergraduate Psychology Association (SUPA), 1978-2002 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Stanford Universal Karate Club, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Stanford University Archery Team, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Stanford University Footbag Club, 1996-2002 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Stanford Univeristy Macintosh User Group, 1984-2000 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - Stanford University Mathematical Organization (SUMO), 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Stanford University Nikkei, 1990-2003 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Stanford University Recording Group, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Stanford University Singers, 1991-2002 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Stanford University Wing Chun Student Association, 1998-2003 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Stanford Upward Bound, 1998-2003 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Stanford Vegan Action, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Stanford Vietnamese Association, 1993-2003 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Stanford Waterski Team, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Stanford Wind Ensemble, 1998-2002 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - The Stanford Wine Circle, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Stanford Women's Club Soccer, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Stanford Women's Squash, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Stanford Women's Ultimate, 1983-2002 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Stanford Wushu Club, 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Stanford Yan Xin Qigong Association, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - Stanford Younglife Leaders Fellowship, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Stanford Youth Forensics, 1996-2002 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - Stanford Youth Project, 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Inactive, 1978-2004
      - A Meeting of the Minds, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - AANSOC Big Sib/Lil Sib Program, 1989-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Abundant Life College Ministry, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Academia and Society Conference, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Actors' Anonymous, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Admiralty Club, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Adopt-A-Class, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - African American Sophomore Class Project, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Afro-Am Discussion Group, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - AIDS Awareness Coalition at Stanford, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - AIDS Awareness Week, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - AIESEC (Association Internationale des Estudiants en Science, Economiques et Comerciales, 1980-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Air.unix Survival Movement, 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - All You Need Magazine, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Alliance for People and Technology (APT), 2000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Alternative Medicine at Stanford, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Aluran Productions, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Amarantos Stanford, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - American Association for the Support of Ecological Initiatives, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - American Bar Association/ Law Student Division, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - American Constitution Society for Law and Policy, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - American Culture Club of Stanford, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - American Studies Student Organization, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Americas + Latinas: A Journal of Women and Gender, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Amici Miei - Italian Stanford Student Association, 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Amigos de las Americas, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Anishinabe, 1993, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Anonymous HIV Antibody Test Peer Counseling, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Anonymous HIV Test Peer Counseling Program, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Art of Living, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Arbor Free Clinic Literacy Project, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Arroyo, 1993-2000 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Asia Pacific Magazine, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Asia Study Trip, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Asian American Activities Center, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Asian American Christian Fellowship, 1988-1998 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Asian American Coalition for Transformation, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Asian American Graduation Committee, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Asian American Journalists Association, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Asian American Voter Registration and Education Project, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Asian Immigration Clinic, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - Asian Business League, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - Asian Pacific Islander Magazine, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Asian Pacific American Policy Form, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - Asian Pacific Islanders for Education and Change at Stanford, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Asociacion de Estudiantes Colombianos, 1993, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Assassin's Guild (Real Life Roleplayers), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Association of Black Education Students (ABES), 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Association of General Contractors (AGC Stanford Chapter), 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - ASSU, 1990-1996 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - ASSU Operating Budget 1989-90 [InterVarsity Christian Fellowship], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - ASSU Shirt Shak, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - August: A Journal, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Aurora, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Ayn Rand Society of Stanford, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - B'Nai Biz, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - The Balance Beam, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Baltic Alliance at Stanford, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Baptist Student Ministries (BSM), 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Bechtel Student Association, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Bechtel International Center Espresso Bar, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Bechtel Student Espresso Bar, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Beyond Heterosexuality Network For Women, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - BCSC Knowledge Bowl Committee, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Big Brothers/Big Sisters, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - Biological Sciences Pre-PhD Club, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Bisexual, Gay, and Lesbians Awareness Days (BGLAD), 1976-1991 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Black Community Service Committee, 1991-2000 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - Black Community Project Fund, 1993-1997 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Black Convocation Organizational Committee, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Black Law Students Association, 1986-1998 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Black Pre-Business Society, 1980-2000 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Black Student Leadership Network, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Blacks in Transition, 1983-1998 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Body Image Awareness Network, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - Body, Image, Food, and Self-Esteem, 1988-1998 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - Branner Presents, 1987-2000 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Brothers at Stanford, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 79)
      - Buddhist Meditation Circle, 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Building Community Day, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      - Business Development Association, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Calendar Club, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Calico Park Entertainment, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - California Alliance of Progressive Student Activists, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - California Students for Bill Bradley - Stanford, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Campus Girl Scouts of Stanford University, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Captain's Council, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Captology Forum, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 89)
      - Cardinal Illustrated, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 90)
      - Cardinal Life, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 91)
      - Casa Zapata, 1992-2000 (Box 8, Folder 92)
      - CASAS (Cuban American Student Association at Stanford), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 93)
      - Celtic-Anglo Club, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 94)
      - Chaparral Cinema - Fridays, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 95)
      - Cheburashka's Committee for Post-Sovietism Conservation, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 96)
      - Chi Alpha Christian Fellowship, 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 97)
      - Chicano Student Activities Committee, 1984-1990 (Box 8, Folder 98)
      - Chicano/a Performance Initiative, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 99)
      - The Chicano/Latino Association of the School of Education (CLASE), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 100)
      - Chicano/Latino Undergrads in Business and International Relations (CLUBIR), 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 101)
      - Chicano/Latino Art Forum, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 102)
      - Chilean Stanford Student Association, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 103)
      - Child Health Advocacy and Awareness, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 104)
      - Children Health and Technology Association, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 105)
      - Children Now at Stanford, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 106)
      - Christian Evangelical Ministries at Stanford, 1979-1990 (Box 8, Folder 107)
      - The Christian Forum, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 108)
      - Christian Life Communities at Stanford, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 109)
      - Christian Student Movement, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 110)
      - Christian Seminars, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 111)
      - Cinco de Mayo Steering Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 112)
      - Class of 1997, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 113)
      - Class of 2002 [Junior and Senior Class Presidents], 1995-2002 (Box 8, Folder 114)
      - Senior Class Presidents, 1991-2000 (Box 8, Folder 115)
      - Club Ujamaa Planning Committee, 1983-1999 (Box 8, Folder 116)
      - Classical Guitar Society of Stanford, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 117)
      - Coalition Against Sexual Assault, 1991-2002 (Box 8, Folder 118)
      - Coalition for Original Music by Stanford Students, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 119)
      - Coalition of Presidents, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 120)
      - Coffee House Live!, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 121)
      - Cognitive Science Graduate Student Society (CSGSS, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - College Republicans for Choice, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Collegiate Leadership Network, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Colostomy Bites, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Committee on Democracy in Education (CODE), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Common Bond, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Communicasians, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Communication Graduate Student Association, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Community Action Coalition, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Community Health Initiative, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Community Integration Network (CIN), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Community Link, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Community Service Representative Network, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Conception, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Conservative Minorities at Stanford (CMAS), 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Constructions, 1989-1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Costano Partnership, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Cowell Cold and Allergy Clinic, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Crealde, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Critical Bitch, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Cross Cultures (formerly HAPA), 1990-1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Current China, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Cyprus Association at Stanford, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - The Daedalus Society, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - The Daily Planet, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Dalmation, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Dance for Health, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Danza Espanola, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - The Daytime Fun Society, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Decision Science Engineering Women (DSE Women), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Defiantly...Kingpins at Stanford, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Derechos (Chicano/Latino Pre-Law Public Policy SO), 1990-2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Dial Tone Student Magazine, 1980-1994 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - The Dingila Medical Relief Project, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Disability Golf Cart Service (DisGoCart), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - The Dish Dash, 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Disordered Eating Education and Prevention Council (DEEPC), 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Diverse Yet Equally Acceptable Lives, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - DOS Facilities, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - The Do It! Magazine Collective, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Doc Talk, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Doctors Ought to Care (DOC), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - DownUnder Club, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Dunai - The Stanford Fold Ensemble, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - EPA Junior Golf / Tutoring Program, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - East Palo Alto Sports, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - East Wind Magazine, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Eco, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Eco-nomy, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - EE Women, 1989-1995 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Elmo, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - El Aguila, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - Emergency Medical Interest Group, 1997-2001 (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - Engineering Annual Spring Awards Banquet Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      - Engineering Entrepreneurs Club, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - Envision Publications, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - ERGO, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - Escondido Village Family Council, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Estos Tiempos, 1984-1990 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Ether, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - European Culture Society, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - EV Community Garden, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - Experimental Music Ensemble, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Faultline, 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 64)
      - Filipino Graduate Students, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Fine Gentlemens Yacht Club, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Fitness Club of Stanford University, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - Flyfish Stanford, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 68)
      - Focus, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 69)
      - Foodnet, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 70)
      - Forward, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      - Foundation on the Rock, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 72)
      - Four Man Suite, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 73)
      - Friends for Life, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 74)
      - Friends of Falun Gong, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 75)
      - Friends of the Link Institute, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 76)
      - Friends of the Free South African Fund, 1987-92 (Box 9, Folder 77)
      - The Funky Finger, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 78)
      - Frog Books, undated (Box 9, Folder 79)
      - Future Social Innovators Network (FUSION), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 80)
      - GAIA, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 81)
      - Gaming Club of Stanford, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 82)
      - Gamma Phi Beta, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 83)
      - Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Business Students Association, 1993-2001 (Box 9, Folder 84)
      - Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Business Students Association, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 85)
      - Gay-Straight Alliance, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 86)
      - The Gender Spot, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 87)
      - Geriatrics Interest Group, 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 88)
      - Gifted Teaching Group of Stanford, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 89)
      - Giving for Tomorrow, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Global Management Program, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Glosses, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Golden Key National Honor Society, undated (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - Govinda, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - Grad Student Council Bulletin, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - Gradnet-Lambda, 1993-2000 (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - Graduate Student Association, 1982-1995 (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - Graduate Students in the Arts, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 98)
      - Graduate Women's Network, 1992-2002 (Box 9, Folder 99)
      - Great Comission Movement - a ministry of Campus Crusade, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 100)
      - Greek Rap, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 101)
      - Groove Theory, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 102)
      - Growth, Integrity, Respect, Learning, Self-Esteem (GIRLS), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 103)
      - GSB Finance and Investment Club, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 104)
      - GSB Catholic Community, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 105)
      - GSB Humor Club, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 106)
      - GSB Israel Study Trip, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 107)
      - GSB Latin America Association, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 108)
      - GSB Multimedia Club, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 109)
      - GSB Public Management Program, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 110)
      - GSB South Asia Trip, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 111)
      - GSB Telecom Club, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 112)
      - GSB Students Against Homelessness, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 113)
      - GSB Thailand/Indonesia Trip, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 114)
      - GSB Venezuela Study Trip, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 115)
      - GSB Volleyball Club, undated (Box 9, Folder 116)
      - GSB Volunteers, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 117)
      - Haas Unifying Board, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 118)
      - Haiduti at Stanford, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 119)
      - Hammer and Coffin Political Action Committee (HAC-PAC), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 120)
      - Hospice Action Volunteer Experience Network, undated (Box 9, Folder 121)
      - Health Library, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 122)
      - Health Matters, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 123)
      - Higher Consciousness, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 124)
      - Herstory, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 125)
      - Highlighters Travelling Theater Troupe, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 126)
      - Hindu Philosophy Discussion Group, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 127)
      - Hindu Students Association of Stanford University, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 128)
      - Hip Hop Nights, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 129)
      - Hiroshima and Nagasaki Awareness Project, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 130)
      - Hispanic Scholarship Fund Scholar Chapter, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 131)
      - History Undergraduate Student Association, 1988-1993 (Box 9, Folder 132)
      - Hoops for Hearts, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 133)
      - Honor Code Reform Initiative, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 134)
      - Hui 'O Hawai'i, 1996-2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Humanist Community, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Hungarian-American Student Association, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Hungarian-American Student Association, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Hwa Rang Tae Kwon Do and Hapkido Club, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Hopkins Marine Station, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Hopkins Marine Station Graduate Student Organization, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - HUGSA Publications, 1986-1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Latino Undergraduate Business Student Association (LUBSA), 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Latino Business Society, 1981-1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Law School Musical Society, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Leadership Education and Development (LEAD) Alumni Association, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - League of East Campus RCCs, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Learning Disabled Students of Stanford (LDSS), 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Lexis, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Lift Every Voice and Sing Inc. (LEV-I), 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - The Little Spark, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - London and the Arts, 1997, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Living History, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Lonestar Republic, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Loose Ends, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Lucid Dreamers Unlimited: Exploring the Real Holodeck Experience, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Maestro Presentations, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Majestic, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Martha Graham Dance Group, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Martin Luther King Jr. Student Association, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Mechanical Engineering Graduate Women's Group, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Medical Student Survival Guide (MSSG), 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Malaysians at Stanford, 1994-2002 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Medicine, Culture, and Communication Project, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Men in Solidarity, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Men Standing Proud and Upright, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Mentorship Program for Stanford Medical Students, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - The Message, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - Methodist Fellowship, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Mighty Pawns, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Moderate Majority, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Montage: The Russian American Student Journal, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Mouth Literary Forum/ August: A Journal, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Mujeres at Stanford, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Musements, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Music Students' Association, 1992-2000 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Na Makana o Hawai'i, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Music Appreciation Society, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - 1998 Mexican and Spanish American Wars Conference Committee, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Nanotechnology Study Group at Stanford, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Naranja House, 1992-2000 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - Narnia, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - National Association for Chicana/o Studies Delegation, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Native American Careers in Health Organization (NACHO), 1985-1993 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Native American Issues League, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Native American Christian Fellowship, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - Native American Law Students Association, 1989-2002 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - National Primary Care Day, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - National Women's Political Caucus of Stanford University, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      - Near East Forum, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 56)
      - Network at Stanford, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      - Neuro- S.I.S., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 58)
      - News Readership Program, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 59)
      - Newman Catholic Community Service Group, 1981-1994 (Box 10, Folder 60)
      - Newspeak, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 61)
      - Nine/Eleven, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      - Nitechat with Peter Szeremi, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Non-Trad Network, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Nordic Ski Club, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Nuestra Graduacion, 1979-2001 (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - Nurk Twins Funclub, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 67)